Alumni Association; Records ua801
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1851-2005; Undated; 3; 10.21 cubic ft.
  - Alumni Day, 1960 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Report to Alumni on the State of the College, 1960 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Memos and Correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Alumni Day, 1961 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Alumni Day, 1962 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Mounted Yearbook Pages, 1962 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Photograph of Students, 1962 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Class Councilors and Board Lists, 1962-1978 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Photograph of Dean Jack Derringer and Henry Jaked, 1963 December 07 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Alumni Day, 1963 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Photograph of the Half-Century Club, 1963 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Distinguished Alumni Award, 1963; 1969; 1976-1978; Undated (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Alumni Branch Handbook, 1964 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Alumni Day, 1964 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Alumni Directory and Unidentified Photograph, 1964 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Carillon with Voice, Alumni Day, 1964 (Reel 1)
  - Class of 1914-1919 Officers, 1964; Undated (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Alumni Day, 1965 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Alumni Association Goals and Planning, 1965-1983 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Ben V. Smith Award, 1965; 1968-1970; 1973; 1976; Undated (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Alumni Day, 1966 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Alumni Manual, 1966 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Homecoming, 1966 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Alumni Publication Samples, 1966-1967 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - James A. Warden Fund, 1966-1984; Undated (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Fannie Hall Delameter '23, 1966; 1970; 1978 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Waverly Place, 1966; 1972-1973; Undated (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Athlete Hall of Fame, 1966-1967; 1970-1971; 1974-1975; 1978-1980; Undated (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Alumni Association Handbook, 1967 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Alumni Council Meeting Photograph, 1967 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Alumni Day, 1967 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Homecoming, 1967 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Martin Luther King Scholarship, 1967-1968; Undated (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Alumni Day, 1968 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Elizabeth Ann Huggins Ballard, 1968 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Homecoming, 1968 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Unidentified Student Photograph, 1968 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - 125th Anniversary, 1968-1969 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Joan D. Van Slyke Fund, 1968-1969 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Alumni Survey, 1968-1970; Undated (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 45-46)
  - Van-Derzee-Pierce Scholarship, 1968-1969; 1974; Undated (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Athletic Council, 1968; 1970; 1973-1975 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Alumni Awards Banquet, 1969 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Alumni Day, 1969 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 50-52)
  - Homecoming, 1969 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - News Clippings, 1969-1971 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Alumni Association Committees, 1969-1971 (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Edith Wallace Fund, 1969-1973; 1981-1982; Undated (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Mildred Schmid, 1969; 1983; Undated (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Alumni Membership Form, ca. 1960s (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Ada Craig Walker Award - [RESTRICTED], 1970; 1977-1985; Undated (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Alumni Day, 1970 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Homecoming, 1970 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Alumni Geographical Distribution, 1970-1972; Undated (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Basketball Scholarship Fund Committee, 1970-1975; Undated (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - History of Alumni Association, 1970; 1983; 1985; 1988; Undated (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Alumni Day, 1971 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Awards Committee, 1971 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Class Affairs Committee, 1971 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Financial Planning Committee, 1971 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Homecoming, 1971 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Photograph of Unidentified Woman, 1971 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Photograph of Upstairs Interior of Alumni House, 1971 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Alumni Membership Dues, 1971-1972; 1974-1975 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Confederation of Alumni Association of the State University of New York, Executive Committee Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Confederation of Alumni Association of the State University of New York, Constitution, Report and Notes, 1971-1973 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19-20)
  - Alumni Travel Programs, 1971-1980; 1984; Undated (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21-24)
  - Insurance Programs, 1971-1972; 1974-1975; 1978; 1981; Undated (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Alumni Day, 1972 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26-27)
  - Alumni Day Photographs, 1972 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Brief History of Alumni Association and Benevolent Association, 1972 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Homecoming, 1972 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Student Photo Contest, 1972 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - American Alumni Council, 1972-1974 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Alumni Association Brochure, 1972; 1974 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Alumni Day, 1973 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Class of 1923 Photograph and Letter, 1973 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Guidelines for Mailings to and Solicitation of Alumni, 1973 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Homecoming, 1973 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Alumni Association Guide, 1973-1974 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Council for Financial Aid to Higher Education, CASE, Survey of Volunteer Support, 1973-1974 (Box 3 (3-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Confederation of Alumni Association of the State University of New York, Correspondence, Minutes and Reports, 1973-1975 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Nold-Miller Printing Co., 1973-1975 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Niagara Mohawk Power Corporation, Correspondence and Reports, 1973-1975; 1977; 1980; Undated (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Photographs of Gary Jones, 1973; 1976; Undated (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Retired Senior Volunteer Program, R.S.V.P., 1973; 1975; Undated (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Alumni Day, 1974 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6-7)
  - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8-9)
  - Eastern Economic Conference Inaugural Convention, 1974 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Homecoming, 1974 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Presidential Search, 1974 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Senior Citizens Day, Programs, Slides and Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Gary Jones, Day Files and Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Ronald R. Schafer Alumni Director, Photographs, Correspondence and News Clippings, 1974-1975; 1978; Undated (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - All Alumni Banquet, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17-19)
  - Alumni Weekend Photographs, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Canary Island Trip Photograph, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Chalk Talk Athletics Luncheon, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Confederation of Alumni Associations, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Council on Advancement and Support Education Award, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Homecoming and Community University Day, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Homecoming and Community University Day Photographs and Negatives, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Inauguration of Emmet B. Fields, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - National Retired Teacher Association, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Personnel Advisory Committee, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Spring Rendezvous, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - SUNY Albany and the Budget Fact Sheet and Draft on Case Statement, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Alumni Geographic Distribution, ca. 1975 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Bicentennial Highlights, 1975-1976 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Basketball Booster Club, 1975-1977 (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Career and Life Planning Task Force, 1975-1976; 1978-1979; Undated (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1975-1976; 1979; Undated (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Council for Advancement and Support of Education, CASE, Correspondence and Memos, 1975-1976; 1980; Undated (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Alumni Association Holiday Cards, 1975-1976; 1983-1984; Undated (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Alumni Membership Forms, 1975; 1978-1986; Undated (Box 4 (3-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Alumni Bicentennial Series, 1976 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Alumni for Environmental Studies, Correspondence, 1976 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Alumni Functions and Staff Photographs, 1976 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Alumni Day, 1976 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4-6)
  - Anniversary Club and Carillion Club Appreciation Dinner Photograph and Negatives, 1976 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Chalk Talk Athletics Luncheon, 1976 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Fulbright Scholars Conference, Correspondence, Roster, Notes and Photographs, 1976 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Homecoming and Community University Day, 1976 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Official State University of New York at Albany Plate, 1976 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Senior Citizens Day, Photographs and Programs, 1976 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Computing Center, Correspondence, Notes and Reports, 1976-1980 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1977 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14-16)
  - Alumni Weekend and Class of 1937 40th Anniversary Photographs, 1977 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - "A Great Place to Be" Pamphlet, 1977 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Homecoming, Community University Day and Parents Day, 1977 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - The Laurie Program and Clip, 1977 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Legislature's Congratulations to SUNY Albany Football Team, 1977 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Gary Jones, Day Files and Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Albany vs. Southern Connecticut Game Program, 1978 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Alumni Association Member Life Insurance, 1978 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1978 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25-26)
  - Alumni Weekend Photographs, 1978 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Gary Jones, Day Files, 1978 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28-29)
  - Marsha J. McCarthy Correspondence, 1978 (Box 5 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30-31)
  - Potter Club Moves, 1978 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - President Vincent O'Leary Inauguration, 1978 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Salvation Army Capital Campaign, 1978 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Career Planning and Placement Brochures, 1978; Undated (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - N.A.T.O., 1978; Undated (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Finance Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Gary Jones, Day Files, 1978-1979 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7-8)
  - Sorrell Chesin Correspondence and Memos [RESTRICTED], 1978-1979 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Edna Schaffer MacAffer PSI Gamma Award, 1978-1979; 1981; 1983-1985; 1987; Undated (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - "At A Glance, Some Distinguished Alumni", 1978-1979; 1984; Undated (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Alumni Directory, 1978-1982; Undated (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12-13)
  - Glen Bumpus Award, 1978; 1980; 1982; 1997; Undated (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Alumni Calendar, 1979 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1979 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16-17)
  - Alumni Weekend Photographs, 1979 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Alumni Weekend, Reunion Banquet, 1979 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - American Vacuum Society Symposium, 1979 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Apollo Conference, 1979 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Comp-U-Card of America, 1979 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Homecoming, 1979 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Marsha J. McCarthy Correspondence, 1979 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Christopher DeComber Scholarship Fund, ca. 1979; Undated (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Photograph of Unidentified Students in Front of Fountain, 1970s (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - President's Club Members, 1970s (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1980 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Alumni Weekend Photographs, 1980 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Gary Jones, Day Files, 1980 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Herb Walther Memorial Scholarship, 1980 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - The Laurie, 1980 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - President Vincent O'Leary Photograph, 1980 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Sauers Recognition Dinner, 1980 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Edna Craig Award [RESTRICTED], 1980-1982; Undated (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Class of 1972 Scholarship, 1980-1983 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Invitations to Receptions and Symposiums, 1980; 1983-1984 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Alumni Office Staff Photograph, 1981 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1981 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Alumni Weekend Photographs, 1981 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Milne Faculty Reunion, 1981 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, 1981; 1994 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Discussion with SUNY-A Alumni Group at David Burke's House, Classes of 1925-1937, 1982 October 12 (Cassette 1)
  - Arthur Collins, Professor of English, SUNYA, Background on Perry D. Westbrook, 1982 November 05 (Cassette 2)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1982 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Alumni Weekend Photographs, 1982 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Alumni Weekend Photograph Slides, 1982 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Chorus Scholae Lahti, Finnish Choir and Photographs, 1982 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - President Vincent O'Leary Photograph, 1982 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - University Mace, 1982 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Nations Capital Alumni Brach Photograph and Unidentified Photographs, 1982; Undated (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Alumni Handbook, ca. 1982 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Class of 1927 Photograph, ca. 1982 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Appreciation Dinner, 1982-1983 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Hospitality Program, 1982-1984; 1986 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - SUNY-A Oral History, Dr. Roger Bancroft, Class of 1934, 1983 April 18 (Cassette 3)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1983 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Capital District Club and Carmina Borana Concert PAC Photograph, 1983 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Gold Coast Chapter Photograph, 1983 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Homecoming, 1983 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - SUNY Alumni Legislative Day Photograph, 1983 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - Reunion Handbook, 1983 (Box 6 (3-Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - Interviews with Evan R. Collins, 1984 March 14 (Cassette 4)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1984 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Alumni Weekend Photographs, 1984 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Carillion Photographs, 1984 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Homecoming, 1984 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Homecoming Photographs and Proofs, 1984 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - President of Alumni Association and Unidentified Individuals Photographs, 1984 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Purple and Gold Induction Ceremony, 1984 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Space Coast Class of 1939 Mini Reunion, 1984 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Student/ Alumni Networking Photographs, 1984 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - University Chorale Concert Invitations, 1984 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - 1985 Alumni Directory, 1984-1989 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11-12)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1985 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Alumni Weekend Photographs, 1985 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Class of 1972 Scholarship, 1985 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Confederation Citation, 1985 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Homecoming, 1985 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Homecoming Photographs and Proofs, 1985 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Mary W. Norton Scholarship Fund, 1985 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Millionth Graduate Celebration, 1985 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Seven Alumni Artists Exhibition, 1985 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Wine and Cheese Tasting Seminar, 1985 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1986 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Alumni Weekend Photographs, Proofs and Negatives, 1986 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24-25)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1987 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Christmas at Alumni House Photographs, 1987 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Distinguished Service Medal, 1987 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Homecoming, 1987 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Homecoming Photographs, 1987 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Minerva Rededications Ceremony, 1987 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Bertha Brimmer Wedding Gown Donation, 1987 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Van Alstyne Posters, 1988; 2003 (Flat-file 1)
  - Lithgow Murals, Milne Library, 1989; Undated (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Photograph of Young Alumni, New York City, 1980s (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Honors Convocation, 1990 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - New York City Boat Cruise, 1990 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Vincent O'Leary Tribute, 1990 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 37-38)
  - Vincent O'Leary Tribute Photographs, 1990 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Florida Space Coast Reunion Lunches, 1990-1996 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - President H. Patrick Swygert Photographs, ca. 1990-1995 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Class of 1936 Reunion Memorabilia, 1991 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Alumni Directory, 1991; 1996 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1991 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Homecoming Photographs and Program, 1991 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - President H. Patrick Swygert Inauguration, 1991 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Alumni Office Staff Photographs, ca. 1991 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Gold Coast Chapter Photograph, 1992 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Homecoming, 1992 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Correspondence, 1992; 1995 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Alumni Day Weekend Brochure Transparencies, 1993 (Oversized 6)
  - Unidentified Photograph, 1993 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Carol Livingston Farewell Luncheon, 1994 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Gold Coast Chapter Reunion Photographs, 1994 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Metro New York Chapter Sesquicentennial Guggenheim Event Photographs, 1994 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Sesquicentennial Alumni Weekend, 1994 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Sesquicentennial Alumni Weekend Photographs, Proofs and Negatives, 1994 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1995 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - President Karen R. Hitchcock Inauguration, 1995 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - President's Recognition Dinner, 1995 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - Alumni Weekend Photographs and Negatives, 1996 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - Culinary Institute Bus Trip, 1997 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - "The Devil's Advocate" Event Photographs, 1997 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 62)
  - Alumni Camp Committee, 1998 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 63)
  - Alumni Honor Roll, 1998 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 64)
  - CD CIA Trip to Vanderbilt, 1998 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 65)
  - Honors Convocation, 1998 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 66)
  - Homecoming Photograph Proofs, 1998 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 67)
  - Purple and Gold Application, 1998 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 68)
  - Alumni Association Sesquicentennial Wine Glasses, 1999 (Artifact-box 1)
  - Homecoming/Family Weekend, 1999 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 69)
  - Party for a Plate Photographs, 1999 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 70)
  - Homecoming, 2000 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 71)
  - Daniel J. Hogarty Jr. Photograph, 2001 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 72)
  - Gala Award Recipients Photographs, 2001 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 73)
  - Big Purple Growl, 2004-2005 (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 74)
  - Alma Mater, Undated (Cassette 5-6)
  - Alumni Association Outline of Functions and Activities, Undated (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 75)
  - Alumni Class of '34, Undated (Cassette 7-8)
  - Alumni Day Response Card, Undated (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 76)
  - Alumni in Front of Coliseum in Rome, Undated (Box 7 (3-Subject Files), Folder 77)
  - Annette De Lysei Photograph, Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Award Recipients Photographs, Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Banners for Alumni Association, Undated (Oversized 7)
  - Banners for Alumni Association Regional Branches - Western New York and W. Central Florida, Undated (Oversized 6)
  - Bertha Brimmer Medal, Undated (Artifact-box 2)
  - Capital District Photographs, Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Carillon Alone, Undated (Reel 2)
  - Carillon Mug, Undated (Artifact-box 3)
  - Carillion Photographs, Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Class Photographs, Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Demonstration, Selections for University of NY on Maas Rowe Symphonic Carillon of 100 Bells and 61 Harp Bells, Undated (Reel 3)
  - Half Century Club, Photograph and Newspaper Clippings, Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Hawley Windows, Library Photographs, Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Historical Note Cards, Contains transcripts of Alumni Meeting Minutes, Undated (Box 8 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)